* Search for:  

Search for:  

Privacy Statement
=================

Who we are
----------

Our website address is: https://dnd5e.info

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
---------------------------------------------------

### Activity Log

This feature only records activities of this site’s registered users, non-registered users are not subject to this data collection.

**Data Used:** To deliver this functionality and record activities around site management, the following information is captured: user email address, user role, user login, user display name, WordPress.com and local user IDs, the activity to be recorded, the WordPress.com-connected site ID of the site on which the activity takes place, the site’s Jetpack version, and the timestamp of the activity. Some activities may also include the actor’s IP address (login attempts, for example) and user agent.

**Activity Tracked:** Login attempts/actions, post and page update and publish actions, comment/pingback submission and management actions, plugin and theme management actions, widget updates, user management actions, and the modification of other various site settings and options. Retention duration of activity data depends on the site’s plan and activity type. [See the complete list of currently-recorded activities (along with retention information)](https://jetpackme.wordpress.com/support/activity-log/#data-retention).

**Data Synced ([?](https://jetpack.com/support/what-data-does-jetpack-sync/)):** Successful and failed login attempts, which will include the actor’s IP address and user agent.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: [https://automattic.com/privacy/](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

We store user input data sent through the contact form on this site, along with meta information about the submissions, including the time stamp, the origin IP address, and the user agent (browser).

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website or other websites. Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit here and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics, Google reCAPTCHA, Google Tag Manager, Jetpack and WordPress.com Stats, and Quantcast Measure to deliver analytical data.

#### Google Analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). The information generated by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  Further information about Google’s privacy policy may be obtained from [http://www.google.com/privacy.html](https://www.google.com/privacy.html).

**Personal Data Collected:** Trackers, Usage data.

#### Google reCAPTCHA

Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Ireland Limited. The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).

**Personal Data Collected:** Usage data, Trackers, Answers to questions, Clicks, Keypress events, Motion sensor events, Mouse movements, Scroll position, Touch events.

#### Google Tag Manager

Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google Ireland Limited.

**Personal Data Collected:** Trackers, Usage data.

#### JetPack and WordPress.com Stats

**Data Used:** IP address, WordPress.com user ID (if logged in), WordPress.com username (if logged in), user agent, visiting URL, referring URL, timestamp of event, browser language, country code. _Important:_ The site owner does **not** have access to any of this information via this feature. For example, a site owner can see that a specific post has 285 views, but he/she cannot see which specific users/accounts viewed that post. Stats logs — containing visitor IP addresses and WordPress.com usernames (if available) — are retained by [Automattic](https://automattic.com/) for 28 days and are used for the sole purpose of powering this feature.

**Activity Tracked:** Post and page views, [video plays](https://jetpackme.wordpress.com/support/for-your-privacy-policy/#video-hosting) (if videos are hosted by WordPress.com), outbound link clicks, referring URLs and search engine terms, and country. When this module is enabled, Jetpack also tracks performance on each page load that includes the Javascript file used for tracking stats. This is exclusively for aggregate performance tracking across Jetpack sites in order to make sure that our plugin and code is not causing performance issues. This includes the tracking of page load times and resource loading duration (image files, Javascript files, CSS files, etc.).

#### Quantcast Measure

Quantcast Measure is an analytics service provided by Quantcast Corporation

**Personal Data Collected:** Trackers, Usage data.

### Subscriptions

**Data Used:** To initiate and process subscriptions, the following information is used: subscriber’s email address and the ID of the post or comment (depending on the specific subscription being processed). In the event of a new subscription being initiated, we also collect some basic server data, including all of the subscribing user’s HTTP request headers, the IP address from which the subscribing user is viewing the page, and the URI which was given in order to access the page (`REQUEST_URI` and `DOCUMENT_URI`). This server data used for the exclusive purpose of monitoring and preventing abuse and spam.

**Activity Tracked:** [Functionality cookies](https://jetpack.com/support/cookies/#subscriptions) are set for a duration of **347 days** to remember a visitor’s blog and post subscription choices if, in fact, they have an active subscription.

Who we share your data with
---------------------------

We do not share your data with anyone unless legally required to, however if you request a password reset, your IP address will be included in the reset email.

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Your contact information
------------------------

You can use the [contact form](https://dnd5e.info/contact/) or email [\[email protected\]](https://dnd5e.info/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Buy the D&D 5th Edition Rules

[

](https://www.amazon.com/dp/0786965606?tag=dnd5einfo07-20)[

](https://www.amazon.com/dp/0786965622?tag=dnd5einfo07-20)[

](https://www.amazon.com/dp/0786965614?tag=dnd5einfo07-20)  
  
_(as an Amazon Associate we earn from qualifying purchases.)_

**DnD5e.info** is owned and coded by [Fortiter Games](https://dnd5e.info/contact). [Privacy Statement](https://dnd5e.info/privacy-statement/).  
  
**Product Identity:** The following items are hereby identified as Product Identity, as defined in the [Open Game License version 1.0a](https://dnd5e.info/legal-information), Section 1(e), and are not Open Content: All proper names, locations, characters, artwork, graphics, and trade dress.  
  
**Open Game Content:** The SRD text on this website is Open Game Content, and is licensed for public use under the terms of [Open Game License version 1.0a](https://dnd5e.info/legal-information). Please [report](https://dnd5e.info/contact) any errors and/or omissions. [Mastodon](https://dice.camp/@FortiterGames)
